Previously on Desperate Housewives...
绝望主妇前情提要...
A call was made.
-电话通了
Sweetie, where are you?
儿子  你在哪儿?
I don't wanna tell you.
-我不想告诉你
And if porter doesn't show up for court,
如果Porter不出庭
We're gonna lose our restaurant!
我们的餐馆就没了
A guy threatens to kill your son,
有人威胁要杀了你儿子
And that's what you're worried about?
你关心的却是这事儿?
And as one love affair blossomed, another...
有人的爱情正如火如荼  而有人的爱情...
You were married before?
-你以前结过婚?
She's dead.
她已经死了
I want you out of my house.
-我要你滚出这个家!
Withered on the vine.
却悄然枯萎
Mike delfino has to pay for taking you away from me.
Mike Delfino必须为此付出代价
I want him to lose what I lost.
我要让他经历我所承受的痛苦
It had been a long journey
对David Williams而言
For david williams,
这是一次漫长的旅途
And though it began years ago,
尽管始于多年以前
He remembered every step of it...
他依然清楚地记得过程中的每一步...
Walking outside his front door
走出自家大门
To find a policeman with news of a car crash...
却发现警察带来车祸噩耗...
Running into the hospital
狂奔去医院
Only to be told
却被告知
His wife and daughter had died...
妻女已经离世...
Being dragged into a psychiatric facility
崩溃之后  被人硬生生
After his mental breakdown...
拽去精神病院...
No!
不!
Strolling into a hotel weeks after being released
出院之后  信步走进一家酒店
And bumping into a beautiful blonde...
却与一位金发美女不期而遇...
Marching down the aisle
与之步向婚姻殿堂
With a woman who, as it turned out,
却意外发现她曾经和那个
Once lived on the same street
让自己家破人亡的男人
With the man who had killed his family.
同住一条街道
But his bride was now unhappy,
现在他的新娘翻脸了
And dave williams was worried
David Williams开始担心
That his dream of revenge had been destroyed.
他的复仇梦想即将破灭
Luckily for dave,
幸运的是
Fate was about to take some steps of its own.
命运打算自己降临
Hey, dave!
嘿  Dave!
What's going on?
你怎么了
Edie and I had a fight.
Edie和我吵了一架
I take it you're giving her time to calm down?
我猜你这是给她空间冷静?
No, I think I'm looking for a place to stay
不  我想我是趁她找律师的时候
While she's looking for a lawyer.
找个地方落脚
Wanna say something helpful, but all I got is "that sucks."
我想说些有用的话  不过我只能说"糟透了"
That it does.
很有帮助
So where are you headed?
那你这是去哪儿
Oh, it's such a nice night,
夜色这么美
I thought I'd walk to that motel on the interstate.
我打算找家汽车旅馆先住住
Might as well enjoy the stars while my life falls apart.
在生活崩塌之时不妨欣赏一下星星
It's getting late, and so, uh...
天色不早了  我还是...
Hey, why don't you stay with me?
不如在我家先暂住一晚?
Really?
真的吗?
I, uh... I wouldn't want to impose.
我...我不想勉强你
Dave, you saved my life.
Dave  你救过我的命
I owe ya.
应该的
Well, now that you mention it, I guess you do.
既然这么说  那我就恭敬不如从命了
Come on in.
进来吧
And just like that,
就是这样
Dave's dream of revenge was salvaged...
Dave的复仇之梦复活了...
Lead the way, roomie.
领路吧  伙计
And he started to feel
他开始感觉
His long journey would soon be over.
这场漫长旅途就要结束了
At 9:02 the next morning...
第二天早上9点过2分...
Edie williams began calling her friends
Edie Williams开始打电话
To let them know
向她的朋友哭诉
Something humiliating had happened to her.
她所经历的奇耻大辱
By 9:06, her friends had begun to arrive,
等到9点过6分  她的朋友开始陆续光临
Just so they could hear the juicy details.
专程来分享其中的惊爆细节
So he was married before.
他以前结过婚
You don't kick a man out for that.
你不能因此就把一个男人赶出家门
No.
是不会
But you do for never mentioning it.
但当他从来没提过时就会
And especially when I laid out my entire past.
亏我还把过去全盘给出(laid out)
Emphasis on the word "laid."
注意"给出"这个词儿(这里的laid指上床)
Oh. Exactly. Gaby gets it.
没错  Gaby说对了
Well, maybe they were only together a short time,
也许他们俩在一起的时间还不长
And she didn't mean anything to him.
她在他心目中的分量也没那么重
I doubt it, since he walks around muttering to her ghost.
我怀疑这点  他还对着她的鬼魂喃喃自语呢
You know what would lift your spirits?
你知道什么会让你精神大振?
We should all do a spa weekend.
-我们应该一起渡过一个SPA周末
Yeah! Let's do that.
说得对极了
Oh, I appreciate the offer,
我深表高兴
But I think I'm better off getting lost in my work.
不过我还是用工作来麻痹自己吧
Well, maybe I can help you. Think you can rent my house out?
也许我能帮你  你能帮我把房子租出去吗?
What?
什么
Jackson got a teaching job at the college in riverton,
Jackson在Riverton的大学里找着了一份工作
And...
然后...
I'm going with him.
我要和他一起去
Uh, wait, you're moving?
等等  你要搬家?
I know it's sudden, but I feel really good about this.
我知道这很突然  但我真愿意这样做
And it's only two hours away,
也不过是两个小时的车程
So it'll still be like we're practically next door.
感觉我们还是离得很近
I am so happy for you, but we're gonna miss you.
我为你感到高兴  但我们会很想念你的
Oh, don't worry about us. Jackson is so great.
别管我们的  Jackson很不错
You are making the right choice.
你做出了正确的决定
Absolutely. Come here, you! Aw!
当然  过来  拥抱一个
I can't believe you're leaving.
真不敢相信你就要走了
Hey! When you're done here, you wanna come do my lawn?
你这边完事了  你想帮忙修理我的草坪吗
Well, I figure since mike's letting me crash here,
我想既然Mike这么好心收留我
It's the least I could do.
-我能做也只有这些了
Well, that's very nice...
那真是既贴心...
And brave. Mike takes a lot of pride in his yard.
又勇敢  这院子让Mike感到特别自豪
Yeah. Look at his roses.
看看这儿的玫瑰
Every time I walk by here, I just want to steal one.
每一次走过这儿  我都想偷一朵
Here, let me cut you one. Oh, no.
-我来给你采一支吧
Mnh-mnh. Couldn't.
不  不用了
He wouldn't like that.
他不喜欢那样
Hey, you. What's up?
怎么啦?
Not much.
没事
Got a call from dylan.
Dylan 给我打电话了
Her husband's traveling more for his business,
她丈夫一直出差忙生意
And she doesn't have anybody to help her with the baby.
而她又没人帮忙照顾小宝宝
She's trying to push me to move out to baltimore.
她想劝我搬去Baltimore
So, uh, what'd you say?
那你怎么说呢?
Oh, just that I'd think about it.
就说会考虑考虑
What do you think I should do?
你觉得我该怎么做?
Well, she really needs your help.
她是真需要你的帮助
I guess you should help her.
我想你应该帮她
Well, I don't know that she needs it.
我不知道她是不是真需要
Honestly? I think she's just lonely.
坦白说  我觉得她只是觉得孤单
Of course... It would be nice to be closer.
当然...离她近一点很好
But is that a good enough reason
但那是个值得我放弃
To uproot my whole life here?
现在生活的好理由吗
What do you think?
你觉得呢
I'm not sure. It's up to you.
我不知道  决定在你
I know. I just...
我知道  我只是...
Thought you might have an opinion.
想你应该会有想法
Oh, shoot. I'm, uh, expecting a call from a supplier.
真不巧  我在等供应商的电话
I'll, uh, I'll talk to you later.
我...我一会再和你说这事儿
On second thought,
仔细想想
I'm sure he won't even notice it's gone.
我猜他都不会发现花儿已经不见了
Of course, this new landscaping
当然  这地方还需要
Will require an updated irrigation system,
安装一套升级的灌溉系统
Which I'm happy to take care of.
-我很乐意效劳
Bree, you bought us a house.
Bree  你已经帮我们买了房子
We can't let you do all this, too.
-我们不能再麻烦你了
Nonsense! It's a small price to pay
胡说  比起让你们的房子
To make your home more beautiful. I insist. Yes!
看起来更漂亮  这不算什么  我坚持
It's gonna be here tomorrow. Whoo-hoo!
明天就会到了  哇哦!
Orson, take it easy!
Orson  冷静点!
Impossible. Soon, i, the grillmaster,
办不到  很快  我  烧烤大师
Will christen a brand-new barbecue.
将很快拥有一个全新的BBQ
You're pretty excited about a grill.
你对个烤架也太过激动了吧
Oh, it's so much more than that, young man.
这可不止于此  年轻人
This is the prairiefire turbo.
它配有超强涡轮
It's 122,000 btus of charbroiling power.
拥有高达12万2千英热的热量(1英热≈1055焦耳)
Look out, cattle!
-牛们  小心着点!
You think you're excited?
一想到卖主对你
Just imagine the salesman who overcharged you.
要价过高  你还激动得起来吗
Well, bree, I got a very good deal.
Bree  这笔买卖十分划算
He only thinks he got a good deal because the salesman
只要卖家他附送一些印有"亲吻厨师"的帽子
Threw in one of those "kiss the cook" hats.
他就会认为这笔买卖赚到了
And the temperature-sensing barbecue fork.
还附有带温度感应的烧烤叉子
Well, that sounds good. Yeah.
听起来不错
Don't encourage him!
别鼓励他
Orson is a horrible negotiator.
Orson是个糟糕的谈判家
He's never met a sticker price he didn't like.
他从来没遇到过不中意的标准定价
Oh, no, bree, that's--
-不 Bree
it's true.
是真的
There's a reason the local car dealers
本地的汽车商每年圣诞节
Send you a fruit basket every christmas.
都送你水果篮是有理由的
Now hush. Mm.
安静
Bree, could you please not do that?
Bree  能不能别那样做?
Do... Do what?
做...做什么?
It's just... When you talk to your husband that way,
只是...当你和你丈夫那样说话的时候
It really pushes a button for me.
让我感到有些不舒服
My mom used to do that, and it, uh...
我妈妈以前也这样做  最后...
Drove my dad away.
我爸爸离开她了
I think he was tired of being emasculated.
他受够了她的强势
Did I mention it has a rear-mounted rotisserie rack?
我跟你说没说它后面还带一个烧烤架?
What exactly are you saying, alex?
你到底在说什么啊  Alex
I'm saying, if you're gonna be rude to your husband,
我在说  如果你要对你丈夫无理的话
Could you just not do it in front of me?
请不要当着我的面这样  好吗?
So rotisserie, huh?
你说烧烤架是吧?
Yeah. Good for chicken, uh...
是啊  鸡肉比较好
Rolled roasts, legs of lamb.
还有烧烤烤肉  羊腿
This thing is so advanced,
这玩意儿太棒了
I could probably use it to make soup.
我还可以用它来煲汤
I'm sorry. Daddy has to work.
对不起  爸爸得去工作
Carlos, what is going on? You're gonna miss your plane.
Carlos  怎么回事  你要误机了
They're upset. They're not used to me being away.
她们很不安  不习惯我不在身边
Oh, for god sakes, girls. It's not lik
我的老天  姑娘们
He's going off to war. He's gonna be back tomorrow.
他又不是去打仗  明天就会回来的
Why can't daddy work here?
爸爸为什么不能在这儿工作?
Because daddy has a new job
因为爸爸有了新工作
That's gonna make us lots of money.
-能赚好多好多钱呢
We don't need lots of money.
我们不需要那么多钱
Hey, what did I say about that kind of language?
我怎么教你们的?
Look, girls...
听着  姑娘们...
Daddy's gonna be home tomorrow in time for dinner.
爸爸明天会按时回家吃饭的
You can call me whenever you want. Okay?
你们可以随时给我打电话  好吗
And the best part is
最开心的是
You get to spend a whole day with just mommy!
你们可以跟妈咪单独呆一整天哦
Oh, hello, mr. Fishman.
你好  Fishman先生
I'm coming in. Watch the wheels.
我要进来了  小心轮子
Boy, you just had to put a rug here, huh?
天呐  你真该在这里铺张地毯
Uh, is everything okay?
一切都还好吗
It's about your damn son.
都是你那个宝贝儿子
Porter?
-Porter?
How the hell do I know?
我怎么知道他叫什么
He's got red hair and he's got a face you just wanna slap,
他长着一头红发和一张让你想抽的脸
And he's driving my sister crazy!
把我的姐姐都快弄疯了
What are you talking about?
-你在说什么
The retirement home.
养老院里
Your kid has been staying in your mom's room.
你儿子一直跟你妈妈住在一起
What?!
-什么?!
Muriel thought he was just visiting,
Muriel以为他只是来看望她的
But he's been there for a week.
但他居然呆了一个星期
Now the rules clearly state...
规定明确指出...
No visiting after dark.
晚间禁止来访
Tom, I know where porter is. He's hiding at my mother's.
Tom  我知道Porter在哪儿了  他藏在我妈妈那里
Oh, hiding, my ass. He's not hiding. He's living there.
"藏"  我的妈呀  他不是藏  是"住"在那儿
He even stole my sister's orange juice.
还偷了我姐姐的橘子汁
I'll take care of it. Thank you.
我会处理的  谢谢
Call bob. Tell him we can make the hearing tomorrow.
打电话给Bob  告诉他我们明天可以去听证会了
Nobody can sleep there
大家都没法睡觉了
Because he's got that tv blaring all night long.
因为他一整晚都把电视声音开的很大
Look, tom, I can't talk now. Just call bob.
听着  Tom  现在不能讲了  打电话给Bob
I'm going over there now. Okay. Bye.
我现在就去那儿  拜拜
Parker, I'm gonna be back in an hour.
Parker  我一小时之内就回来
Mr. Fishman, thank you so much.
Fishman先生  非常感谢
Well, don't just stand there. Make me a sandwich!
别傻站着啊  给我做个三明治去
Uh, one more thing.
还有一件事
Could you see about having the basement cleared out?
你看能不能清理一下地下室呢
Yeah, the last time we went down there,
是的  上次我们下去的时候
It was filled with mildewed boxes.
-发现很多发了霉的纸盒子
Oh, I'll take care of that.
好的  我会处理的
There's nothing worse than having old junk around.
没什么比一堆旧垃圾在周围更恶心的了
Edie!
Edie
Case in point.
最佳例证
Edie?
Edie!
Edie
Do you not hear me?
没听见我叫你吗
Yeah, I heard you. Why do you think I kept walking?
听见了啊  你觉得为什么我没停下呢
Looks like the mailman switched our mail again.
貌似邮差又把我们的邮件弄混了
Do you have mine?
你拿到我的了吗
Yep. It's in my garbage.
拿了啊  丢垃圾箱里了
Come by and grab it at your convenience.
方便的话随时过来拿啊
What is wrong with you?
你到底怎么了
I asked everyone over this morning
今天早上我把大家都叫来
Because I had this huge thing to share
因为我要告诉大家
About kicking my husband out, and you prance in
关于把我老公扫地出门的重大决定  而你
With your, "me and jackson are moving to a fairy castle."
却插一句"我和Jackson要搬去我们的梦幻城堡了"
I'm sorry. I thought we gave your latest breakup
对不起  我以为我们给了你的最新分手资讯
The three seconds of shock it deserved.
三秒钟的关注度  它也就值那几秒钟
Get the hell out of here.
-给我滚出去
Gladly.
非常乐意
What have you done?
你干了什么
Nothing. It's locked.
什么也没做  它锁住了
Do you have a key?
有钥匙吗
In my purse.
在我包里
Which I left in the kitchen.
我把它放在厨房了
Does anyone know you're here?
有人知道你在这儿吗
No.
不
Oh! Hey! Help!
救命啊
Somebody help me!
来帮帮忙
Get me out of here!
救我出去
Juanita, it's time for your bath.
Juanita  该洗澡了
I'm watching my movie.
-我在看电影
You've seen it a hundred times.
你看了N次了
She loses her shoe, the prince finds it--end of story.
她丢了鞋  王子找到了...故事结束
Let's go.
-走吧
I'll go when I'm ready.
我想去了就去
Hey, it's not finished!
-还没完呢!
It is for you. Now move!
对你来说完了  快去!
Juanita Solis, I am not kidding.
Juanita Solis  我没跟你开玩笑
Okay. That does it.
好吧  那这样
Juanita.
Juanita
If you think I'm not gonna drag you to the bathroom,
如果你以为我没法把你弄到浴室去
You are sadly mistaken!
那就大错特错了
You're never gonna make it.
-你办不到的
Oh, yes, I will.
我会办到的
My rage is fueling me in ways you can't imagine.
我的愤怒从我身上的每个毛孔给我加足了火力
What's wrong?
怎么了?
My rage just needs to catch its breath.
我的愤怒需要喘口气
Okay. Okay.
好啦  好啦
I am willing to forget this entire incident
如果你现在就跳进澡盆里的话
If you just go jump in that bathtub right now.
刚才的事情就一笔购销
What do you say?
怎么样
I am gonna scrub that smug look right off your face.
我要把你的一脸得意狠狠地洗掉
Aah! Oh, my back! Aah! Aah!
我的腰啊
Where is he?
他在哪儿?
I'm sorry. Have we met?
不好意思  我们认识吗
Wait...
等等...
You're the girl who stuck me here three years ago.
你就是三年前把我丢在这里的女孩儿吧
You come by every christmas and look at your watch
你每年圣诞都过来  在我拆封你
While I unwrap the socks you bought me on the drive over.
在路上买来送我的袜子时  还一个劲儿地看表
Do you know what's going on with porter? The fire? The arrest?
你知道Porter发生什么了吗  那场火灾  被捕入狱?
Yes. I read the newspapers.
知道啊  我看了报纸的
Everybody's crying for that poor kid's blood.
每个人都希望这可怜的孩子血债血偿
No, no. We have this great lawyer.
不  不是  我们请了个很好的律师
He thinks he can get the case thrown out.
他说他能让这个案子被撤销
Oh, really? I didn't realize that.
真的吗  我不知道
Oh... Porter! Come out from under the bed!
Porter  从床底下出来吧
Mommy is here to take care of you!
妈咪来这里照顾你了
Just like she took care of me.
就像她照顾我一样
Okay. I know you're mad.
好吧  我知道你很生气
I know we have a lot to hash out between us.
我知道我们之间有太多的事情需要解决
But don't take your hate for me out on your grandson.
但请不要把对我的怨气撒在你的孙子身上
Now where is he?
他到底在哪儿
He's safe.
他很安全
I heard muriel fishman rat me out to her brother,
我听说Muriel Fishman到她弟弟那里告我的状
So i-i made sure that porter cleared out.
所以我只能把Porter弄出去了
Mom...
妈妈...
This is wrong.
这样做不对
Please.
拜托了
Sucks to feel powerless, doesn't it, lynette?
力不能及的感觉很糟糕吧  Lynette
Please, help!
拜托  救命啊
Please!
拜托
Wow. I'm getting a really unpleasant picture
我开始能想象你要是玩
Of what you're like in the ol' sackarooni.
办公室偷情会是什么样子了
Face it, mayer. We're stuck.
面对现实吧  Mayer  我们被困住了
Gotta get out.
总得出去啊
I'm supposed to be meeting the moving company.
我约了搬家公司的
What?
怎么了
Keep talking about how
继续讲你打算
You're going to move away and be with jackson.
怎么搬去和你的Jackson一起共筑爱巢吧
I hear stupidity makes time go faster.
我可以听一些蠢事打发一下无聊时光
So now me wanting to be with the man I love is stupid?
所以说我想搬去和我爱的人一起住很蠢喽?
And needy and pathetic and...
很囧很可悲...
Kinda hilarious.
也有点可笑
But there's one thing it's not, mayer.
但有个词我绝不会用  Mayer
That's "unexpected."
就是"出乎意料"
What are you getting at?
你想说什么?
Have you ever in your life been without a man?
你的生活中有过没有男人相伴的时间吗
Of course I have.
当然有啦
When?
-什么时候?
I don't know. I'm not sure.
我不知道  不确定
What are you doing?
你要干什么
Making a calendar.
做个时间表
Edie...
Oh, come on. We've got nothing but time,
得了吧  我们有的是时间
And I assume you don't wanna make out, so...
我猜你也不想和我亲热  所以...
First boyfriend?
第一任男友?
Todd shaffer. I was 14.
Todd Shaffer  我14岁
And why did you and hot toddy break up?
那你为什么跟性感Toddy分手呢
He dumped me during math class.
他在数学课上把我给甩了
And how long did it take you to start dating somebody else?
你过了多久才开始跟别人约会?
This is a stupid exercise. I refuse to--
这个测试真愚蠢  我拒绝...
When was it?
什么时候?
Lunch. It was lunch.
午饭  吃午饭的时候
You know, I'm feeling a bit randy tonight.
知道吗  今晚我感觉有点欲火焚身
What do you say we make a little love?
你觉得我们小小嘿咻一下如何?
Well, we've got 15 minutes till the news is on. Why not?
离新闻开始还有15分钟  为什么不呢
I still can't get over the way alex behaved this morning.
我还是没法忍受Alex今天早上的表现
"emasculating." I've never heard such nonsense.
"阉割"  我从来没听过这种谬论
Don't you think so?
你不是这样想吗
Well, I thought the matter in which alex made his point
我觉得Alex阐明他观点的方式
Was inappropriate.
有些不太合适
But?
但是?
Well, I wouldn't say it was nonsense.
我不觉得全是谬论
You can be a little tough sometimes.
有时候你是有点过于强硬
"tough"?
"强硬"?
That's not a word I would use to describe myself.
我可不会用这样的词来形容自己
Nobody blames you, bree.
没人怪你  Bree
You run a business. You have to be formidable.
你经营一份事业  没办法不强硬
Sometimes, if that frame of mind carries over
有时候  如果这种强硬传递到了
Into your personal life, it's only to be expected.
你的个人生活中  也没什么大不了的
I don't think I do that.
我觉得我没有啊
I know you don't. It's not worth getting upset about.
我知道你没有  不值得你为这点事不高兴
Andrew and I are used to it,
Andrew和我已经习惯了
And I'm sure in time, alex will get used to it, too.
我相信在将来  Alex也会习惯的
Now... On to more pleasant things.
现在...该做点儿更舒服的事了
Even though it's my turn, I don't mind if you're on top.
虽然轮到我了  我还是不介意你在上面
I think we forgot one.
我觉得我们漏了一个
Didn't you date somebody after you stole karl away from me?
在把Karl从我这偷走后  你不是又跟一个人约会了吗
Ron. Dr. Ron.
Ron  Ron医生
Are we done?
弄完了吗
Yep. Here it is--the history of your love life.
好了  完成了  你的罗曼史
Proof that you can't be happy without a man.
你没有男人就不开心的证明
This is not proof of anything.
这什么都证明不了
Seven boyfriends through high school and college--
从高中到大学你交了七个男友
Only... 41 days single.
只有...41天单身
What does that tell you?
-这能说明什么呢
My grades sucked?
我的成绩差极了?
It's a cry for help, mayer.
这是求救的呼声啊  Mayer
And it doesn't get much better
在你成年之后的十几年里
Into the many decades of your adulthood.
情况也一点没有改变
Hey, I was single for several months after karl
在Karl和Mike之后我可是单身了
And after mike.
好几个月
But that wasn't of your choosing.
那不是出于你的选择
They dumped you.
是他们甩了你
I know. It's hard to look in the mirror.
我知道  反省自己总是很难的
Have you ever looked in your mirror, edie?
你反省过自己吗  Edie?
You're famous for the number of men you've conquered.
你征服男人的数量可是让你名扬天下呢
Thank you.
谢谢
It's not a compliment, you tramp!
这不是夸你  你这个荡妇
Okay, I am not gonna take relationship tips
好了  我是不会让一个
From a woman who has hooked up with...
跟超过一千个男人鬼混过的女人
What is it? Over a thousand men?
来指点我的感情问题呢
Okay, that's true. I enjoyed the '80s.
好了  这倒不假  我享受那段时光
But the difference is,
不同的是
I go after men because I want them.
我找男人是因为我想要他们
You go after them because you need them.
你找男人是因为你需要他们
That is not much of a distinction.
这没什么区别啊
Yes, it is. You have holes in your heart
不  这是有区别的  你的心中有缺口
That can only be filled by a pair of trousers.
你需要男人来填补你的缺口
Face it, mayer. You're weak.
直面现实吧  Mayer  你很软弱
Porter wasn't there,
Porter不在那儿
And she won't tell me where he is.
她不会告诉我他的下落的
Did you tell her that he could end up in jail?
-你告诉她那小子可能要坐牢吗
Of course I did.
当然告诉她了
Lynette, you're really upset. Just hang up and come home.
Lynette  你很不安  挂了电话回家来吧
She's so angry at me.
她太生我的气了
She's never gonna tell us where he is.
她是不会告诉我们他在哪儿的
Lynette?
Lynette?!
Uh, we need to find lynette scavo.
我们要找Lynette Scavo
Let me check.
-我看一下
This is all my fault.
都是我的错
She was so worked up when she left my room.
她离开的时候太激动了
I'm not finding a lynette scavo.
没有一个叫Lynette Scavo的
Oh, my god. Does that mean she's dead?
我的上帝啊  这是不是意味着她死了?
No.
不
不是
It means she outsmarted her mom.
这意味着她比她妈妈聪明
Oh, my god, porter, we missed you so much.
天哪  Porter  我们太想你了
I-i don't understand. I thought you were in an accident.
我...我不太明白  我原以为你出事了
No, sweetie. I was driving home last night,
没有  宝贝儿  我昨天晚上正开车回家
Talking with your dad on the phone,
跟你爸爸打电话
And two cars in front of me had an accident.
前面的两辆车撞了
And I thought, damn, that could be me.
我就想  该死  出事的有可能是我
And then I thought, that could be me.
然后我又一想  那可以是我
You scared the hell out of me.
-你吓死我了
We are sorry, but we had to get you back.
对不起  但是我们必须把你找回来
You've gotta be in court by 5:00.
-你5点钟的时候要出庭
No! I don't want to go to jail.
不  我可不想坐牢
Porter, listen to me. Bob talked to the judge.
Porter  听我说  Bob跟法官谈过了
He thinks he can get them to drop the charges.
他觉得他可以让他们撤销指控
I don't know if I should believe you.
我不知道该不该相信你
You're gonna have to.
你必须要相信我
Okay.
好吧
Great. Come on. Let's go.
太好了  来吧  咱们走
That was a rotten thing you did, lynette.
你这招真龌龊  Lynette
I thought you were dead.
我还以为你死了
Yeah, well, what can I tell ya?
是呀  我还能说什么呢
I learned from the best.
老师教得好
Celia! Juanita!
Celia  Juanita
I am not gonna ask you again to pick up these clothes!
把衣服捡起来  我不想再说第二遍了
You've got till the count of three!
我数三声
One...
1...
Two...
2...
You can hear me, right?
你听到我说的话了  对吧
All right, that's it! I'm calling your father!
好了  够了  我要给你们爸爸打电话
You are gonna get it now!
你们等着吧
He is gonna tear into you! It is gonna be a bloodbath!
他会把你揍扁的  就跟大屠杀一样
Hey, babe. What's up?
宝贝儿  怎么了?
It's your children. They've run amok.
管管你的孩子  她们快玩疯了
What?
-什么
Now that you've gone back to work,
你去工作之后
They won't listen to me.
他们就不听我的了
They know you're not in the next room, ready to drop the hammer.
他们知道你不在隔壁  随时准备收拾她们了
Help me!
-帮帮我
How? I'm in a meeting.
怎么帮?  我正在开会
O-okay. I'm gonna put you on speaker,
好了  我把免提打开
And I want you to rip 'em a new one.
我要你们好好收拾她们
I'm with clients. I don't have time for this
我跟客户在一起呢  没时间干这个
But--
-但...
I gotta go!
我要挂了
Carlos? Carlos!
Carlos?  Carlos!
I think he hung up, mommy.
他挂电话了  妈妈
Can you bring us a lemonade?
能给我们拿杯柠檬汁吗
Hi, mike.
Mike
Hey, sorry I'm late. Where's katherine?
抱歉  我迟到了  Katherine在哪儿?
Ah, headache. She sends her regrets.
她说她头疼  她很抱歉
You mind if I grab a beer?
-介意我拿杯啤酒吗
Uh, yeah. In the test kitchen.
去拿吧  在试验厨房
Uh, beer sounds good. I think I'll grab one, too. Excuse me.
啤酒不错啊  我也要来一杯  失陪了
So... Katherine not feeling well, huh?
Katherine不舒服吗
Yeah, I think she also might be a little miffed with me.
是呀  我想她也有点儿生我的气
This about baltimore?
是关于Baltimore的事吗
It's not that I want her to go, 'cause I don't.
我不是想让她走  我不想让她走
They why don't you tell her?
那为什么不跟她说?
I don't wanna be the guy
我不想成为
That comes between her and her daughter,
夹在她和她女儿中间的那个人
Not to mention a grandchild.
更别提还有一个第三代了
I thought this was because...
我原以为这是因为...
I don't know.
我也不知道
Maybe you're still hung up on your ex-wife.
也许你还放不下你的前妻
Susan?
No. No, that's over.
不  不  那已经结束了
You sure?
你确定?
And most guys I talk to,
跟我谈过的大部分男人都说
They say they only really fall in love once.
他们只会真正坠入一次爱河
And even if it doesn't work,
即使没办法实现的话
They spend the rest of their lives
他们在余生之内
Thinking about the one that they lost.
都会想着他们失去的那一个
I always wondered if that's how you felt about susan.
我一直想知道你是不是也对Susan有这样的感觉
Why would you wonder about something like that?
你为什么想知道这个?
Oh, I don't know.
我也不知道
You're my friend. I care about you.
你是我的朋友  我关心你
Well, no.
不是
In fact, dave,
其实  Dave
I think I might be falling in love with katherine.
我觉得可能爱上Katherine了
Did you just use the "l" word? Oh.
你是不是刚刚用了那个带"l"的单词?
Wow! See, i-i didn't realize it was that serious.
我没想到你这么认真
Well, to be honest,
说实话
It didn't really hit me until she said she might leave.
直到她说也许会离开时我才意识到
Where are our guests?
我们的客人们呢
The food's gonna get cold.
再不来吃的就凉了
Oh, I'll go find them.
我去叫他们来
And bring some steak sauce. Oh,
带些牛排酱来
You're not gonna need any sauce with these babies
这些烤肉可不需要那玩意儿
They are seasoned to perfection.
它们的味道简直是完美的
Bring it.
拿点过来
Well, there's no sense in waiting. Dig in.
没什么必要继续等了  开吃吧
Oh, dear. Are they overcooked?
天哪  是不是烤过头了?
No, they're well-done. That's the way I like them.
没有呀  挺好的  我就喜欢这样的
Bree, what do you think?
Bree  你觉得怎么样
Oh, I really couldn't say.
我不好说
You couldn't say if your meat is overcooked?
你不好说肉到底有没有烤过头?
No. I wouldn't want to upset anyone.
不  我不想令任何人不开心而已
Well, don't worry. You won't upset me.
不用担心  你不会打击到我的
I don't think she was referring to you.
我想她指的不是你
Well, it's just that grilling is such a manly pastime.
只是烤肉是这么有男子气概的事情
If I suggested that orson somehow failed
如果我说Orson没能
To produce the perfect steak,
烤出完美的牛排
You might see it as another example of emasculation.
你可能会把它当成我作威作福的另一个例子
I see. You're not gonna let that go, are you?
我明白了  你不会放过那件事的  不是吗
Well, for all I know,
据我所知
Telling orson his steak tastes like charcoal
告诉Orson他做的牛排尝起来像木炭一样
Might be deballing him.
很损他的气概
You know, bree, you can make your point and still be nice.
Bree  其实你可以礼貌而婉转地表达你的观点
You know what else would be nice, alex?
知道还能怎样表现的礼貌吗  Alex
Showing gratitude when people have been generous with you.
向对你很慷慨的人表示一些感激
Don't listen to her, alex.
别听她的  Alex
She's not mad at you. She's mad at me... And the meat.
她不是生你的气  她是生我的气...生肉的气
Gratitude? What do you mean by that?
感激?  你什么意思?
I mean I bought you a house.
我的意思是我给你们买了座房子
You'd think you'd show me a little respect.
你应该对我表示起码的尊重
Seriously? You're bringing up the house?
你当真?  拿那房子说事儿?
Well, why not? It was a fairly grand gesture on my part.
为什么不呢  这是我为示好而做出的很大的行动
Yes, and one that apparently comes with strings.
是呀  很明显这里是有代价的
If by "strings," you mean
如果"代价"指的是
I won't let you be rude to me in my own house, then yes.
我希望你不要在我家里对我这么无礼  那么你说对了
You know what?
你知道吗
I think I'm going to have to decline your grand gesture.
我想我不得不拒绝你的好意了
Keep the house.
留着你的房子吧
What's wrong?
怎么回事?
Orson burnt the steaks.
Orson把牛排烤焦了
Susan, how can you tell if pickles have botulism?
Susan  怎么分辨酱菜有没有发霉?
Ah, what the hell?
管它呢
I shoot this stuff into my forehead.
我闻一下就知道了
Forget it.
还是算了吧
I'd rather starve for a day or two.
我宁愿饿一两天
By then, you'll be dead,
到时候你就已经死了
And I can use your remains as a source of protein.
你的尸体可以给我提供蛋白质
Oh, come on. That was funny.
拜托  那挺好笑的
You know...
知道吗
Maybe I do feel incomplete without a man.
也许没男人的时候我是觉得空虚
But i... Wouldn't trade places with you for anything.
但无论怎样我都不会跟你对换位置的
You wanna know why?
你想知道为什么吗
No, but I'm trapped, so knock yourself out.
不想  但既然被困在这里了  你想说就说吧
It's the way you are with men--
是因为你对待男人的方式...
They're like tissues.
你把他们当手纸一样
You use one and then toss it away,
用完就扔
And then you're on to the next one.
然后继续下一个
At least I'm looking for something real.
至少我在寻找一些真实存在的东西
So you think this happy ending crap
所以你觉得"从此幸福地生活在一起"
That you believe in is real?
这种鬼话是真的喽?
Please. I know what men are really like.
拜托  我清楚男人都是什么货色
Really?
是吗
Well, when I was 16, my dad had an affair
我16岁的时候  我爸爸有了外遇
With this woman who had a 10-year-old daughter.
那个女人有个10岁的女儿
And one day, he told my mom and me
一天  他告诉我和我妈妈
That he was leaving us for them.
他要离开我们跟她们在一起
Oh, my god.
我的天哪
No talking.
别说话
A week later, he comes to the house to get his stuff,
一周以后  他回家来收拾他的东西
And my mom didn't want to see him,
我妈妈不想见他
So we went to the movies.
就带我去看电影了
Now I had this, uh, horse figurine collection.
那时候我收集了各种各样的小马雕像
Plastic, glass, ceramic--
塑料的  玻璃的  陶瓷的...
Hundreds of them.
好几百个
Anyway, we come back from the movies,
总之  我们看完电影回家
And my dad had taken all his stuff. So...
我爸爸已经收拾完东西走了
I go into my bedroom, and something seems different.
当我走进我的卧室的时候  发现有点不一样
And then I realize all of my horses were gone.
然后我发觉我所有的马都被拿走了
My mom called my dad and screamed,
我妈妈给我爸打电话吵了一架
And all he said was, I was too old for them
他只是说  我已经过了玩那些东西的年龄
And that his girlfriend's daughter
他女朋友的女儿
Would appreciate them more.
比我更适合玩它们
Can you believe that? What a fungus.
你能相信吗  简直一派胡言
Oh, god. Are you crying?
我的天哪  你在哭吗
It's just...
只是...
Now I get it.
我现在明白了
Get what?
明白什么
All these years, I have judged you,
这么多年  我都对你有成见
And... It is not your fault.
可那并不是你的错
Oh, come here.
过来抱抱
You are the way you are because of your father.
你之所以这样都是因为你老爸
Edie, what the hell?!
Edie  这怎么搞的?!
Don't psychoanalyze me, you simp!
别对我做心理分析  你个蠢货
I was just trying to tell you how selfish men are.
我只是想告诉你男人都很自私
And I was just trying to be nice
我只是想对你好点
And give you a free pass for being such a big slut!
给你荡妇一样的所作所为找个好借口
Aah! No!
不!
Edie!
Okay, girls.
好了  女孩们
Pick up your toys and put 'em in the basket before dinner.
晚饭前把这些玩具都收拾到筐里去
Dinner's not for two hours.
离晚饭还两个小时呢
I've had enough of your crap. Now pick up these toys!
哪来那么多废话  现在就收拾玩具!
No!
不!
Okay, juanita. What is going on here?
好了  Juanita  这都怎么回事?
Why are you being so difficult?
你为什么这么不听我的话?
When daddy asks you to do something, you just do it.
你爸爸让你干什么的时候  你从来都很听话
That's because I love daddy more.
因为我更爱爸爸
Fine.
好吧
Everything okay, mrs. Solis?
一切都好吗  Solis太太?
Yeah. Just my kids.
是的  只是我的小孩儿
They really know how to push my buttons.
她们真是让我毫无办法
Oh, yeah. I got a couple monsters at home, too.
我家里也有些捣蛋鬼
The key is, you gotta be the bigger monster.
关键是  你要镇得住他们
Well, unfortunately,
不幸的是
They're not afraid of me.
她们不怕我
Ooh, that's bad.
那太糟了
Fear is the foundation of all good parenting.
做好父母的基础就是要让孩子怕你
You gotta practice your big voice.
你得练练怎么吼他们
Finish that broccoli now!
把那些椰菜给我吃完!
You see how that works?
看到了吗
Yeah. It's very effective.
看到了  很管用
Hey, you got an extra 15 minutes?
你有额外的15分钟吗
Do it! Faster! Faster!
快做!  快点!  快点!
Faster!
快!
I wanna see this place sparkle!
我要看到这里干干净净的
Mommy...
妈妈...
It's out of my hands, girls.
我也管不了啊  孩子们
Word got out that you were disobeying,
听说你们一点都不听话
And they sent reggie over.
-他们就把Reggie派来了
Who sent reggie over?
谁派来的?
Well, I know how much you love him, but...
我知道你们很爱你们的爸爸  但是...
It was your daddy.
就是你爸爸派来的
Enough chatter. Keep moving!
聊够了吧  继续干活
When they're done,
等她们干完了
You want me to make them vacuum?
你要不要我让她们把地也吸了?
If you wouldn't mind.
-如果你不介意的话
Nah.
当然
Guess.
猜
Aw, come on, edie. I said I was sorry.
拜托  Edie  我说过了我很抱歉
Guess!
猜
July?
七月?
Wrong. March!
错  三月!
Man,you're bad at this.
你也太差劲了
Guess.
猜
Oh, hey, mrs. Williams. I didn't know you were down here.
Williams太太  我不知道你在这儿啊
Oh, thank god! We've been locked in here all night.
谢天谢地  我们一整晚都被锁在这儿
Really? Good thing I came by to check the rat traps then.
是吗  那多亏我过来检查捕鼠夹啊
Ugh! I'm glad I forgot about those until now.
很高兴我现在才知道还有这玩意
Uh, mayer?
Mayer
I, uh, would appreciate it
如果你不把
If you wouldn't talk about what we talked about.
我们的谈话内容告诉别人我将不胜感激
I wasn't planning to.
本来就没想告诉别人
Good, because I'll deny it if you do.
很好  即使你说了我也会否认的
I won't.
我不会说的
And... I'll kill you.
否则我会杀了你
Good-bye, edie.
再见  Edie
Oh, I'll bring your mail over when I get home.
我回家的时候会把你的信带过去的
Thanks.
谢了
Hey, mom.
妈妈
I just came by to tell you
我来是告诉你
That the judge threw out porter's case
法官撤销了对Porter的起诉
For lack of evidence. Isn't that great?
因为证据不足  太好了不是吗
Mom...
妈妈...
I did not put you in here to punish you.
我送你进来不是为了惩罚你
I didn't have a choice.
我没的选择
You had a choice.
你有选择的
No, I didn't.
不  我没有
From the moment glen died, you were out of control.
Glen死后  你就失去了控制
It's true you lost all that money in vegas.
你在维加斯输掉了所有的钱是事实
You started drinking again.
你又开始酗酒
And how many times did I go to your condo, only to find you
还有多少次  我到你的公寓  却发现你
Asleep on the sofa with a cigarette in your mouth?
昏睡在沙发上  嘴里还叼着烟
No, I won't apologize for bringing you here.
不  我不会为送你进来而道歉
I did it because I love you.
我那么做是因为我爱你
Then why don't you come visit me?
那你为什么不来看我?
It's not a very pleasant experience.
到这来的经历可不怎么愉快
So I yell a little. So I toss a few curse words your way.
没错我是大声吼了你  对你说了些难听的话
Big deal!
很严重吗
Last time I came, you threw pudding at me.
我上次来的时候  你拿布丁扔我
I'm an angry old woman, lynette! What do you expect?
我是个愤怒中的老女人  Lynette  你希望我怎么做?
Here's a thought-- stop being angry.
我希望你别再生气了
How?
怎么做?
I can't make a friend in this place
在这儿我交不到一个朋友
Without having them drop dead of a stroke five minutes later.
他们都说不定五分钟后就会中风而死
I-i feel like hell.
这简直就像地狱
Every time I look in the mirror, I wanna scream.
每次我照镜子  都想要放声尖叫
My anger is all I've got left, baby.
我剩下的就只有愤怒了  孩子
If I let go of that, it's over. I know it.
如果连这也放弃  就完了  我知道的
The ball game will be over.
我这一生就都结束了
The ball game is going to end
人生总会有尽头的
Whether you like it or not.
不管你喜不喜欢
I would like to be here with you for whatever time you have left.
不管你还剩下多少时间  我都愿意陪在你身边
But for that to happen, things have to change.
但前提是你必须有所改变
Would you come visit me more often?
你愿意多来看看我?
At least twice a week,
至少两周一次
And sometimes I'd bring the kids.
并且我会时不时带孩子们一起来
I'd like that.
我喜欢这样
You know, they turned out really good.
他们真的都是好孩子
How'd you learn how to be such a good mom?
你是怎么学会做一个好妈妈的?
I have no idea.
我不知道
Well, now that you're here,
既然你都来了
Why don't you stay, and we can talk a while?
-不如就留下  我们多聊一会吧
Okay.
好啊
I--and get my flask out of the drawer.
我...去把酒瓶从抽屉里拿出来
Hey, I can't be nice, forgiving and sober all at the same time.
我可不能一下子同时做到态度好  谅解你  戒酒
Daddy!
爸爸
Mmm! Mwah! Missed you guys.
想死你们了
Wow! You're really helping mommy, huh? That's great.
你们真的在帮妈妈做事嘛  真不错
The scary man told us we had to.
那个吓人的大叔命令我们的
We don't even know the guy.
我们甚至不认识那个人
He left a flier in our mailbox. You left him do your parenting?
他往我们邮箱送了张传单  你就让他帮你管教孩子了?
Hey, you're the one who told me to get creative.
-是你让我自己想办法的
This wasn't what I meant!
这可不是我的本意
Easy for you to say. They told me they love you more than me.
说得容易  她们说比起我  她们更爱你
And when I was running things, they said they loved you more.
由我负责家事的时候  她们说的是更爱你
Really?
真的吗
So don't get your feelings hurt,
所以别觉得受伤了
And stop asking strangers to discipline our kids.
也别再让陌生人来教我们的孩子了
Well, I wouldn't have to if you would do it.
好吧  如果你愿意管她们我也不会这样
So you want me to go to work all day, go out on business trips,
这么说你希望我整天出去工作  去出差
And what little time I have here with the girls,
而我唯一跟孩子们在一起的一点时间
You want me to spend screaming at them?
你还要我朝她们吼?
Just for the first 15 minutes after you walk in the door.
只限于你进门后的15分钟
Then it's carlos time.
-之后就是亲子时光
Forget it! This was the arrangement you wanted.
想都别想  这都是你一手安排的
You made me take this job.
-是你让我接下这份工作
I just wanted us to have a normal life.
我只希望我们的生活恢复正常
Well, guess what, sweetie? Dad's unhappy at work.
猜猜怎么着  甜心  爹地上班不愉快
Mom's home with the screaming kids. You got one.
妈咪在家应付调皮的孩子  有你的
Oh, good. You're back.
很好  你回来了
Can we talk?
我们能谈谈吗
If it's about work, yes.
如果是关于工作的  可以
If it's about what happened at the barbecue, no.
如果是关于烧烤会上的事  不了
Fine. Then as my employee, I authorize a 5-minute break
好吧  那作为我的员工  我准许你休息5分钟
So we can talk about my son's boyfriend
好让我们谈谈我儿子的男朋友
And his absurd overreaction this afternoon.
和他今天下午荒谬的过度反应
That's it. I'm out of here.
够了  我要走了
Andrew, please. You were there. Alex started the whole thing.
Andrew  拜托  你也在那  事情都是Alex引起的
You need to tell him to stop criticizing me.
你得告诉他别再批评我的做法了
I'm--i'm not getting in the middle of this.
这事我不会插手的
If you have a problem with alex, you tell him.
如果你和Alex有问题  你自己去跟他说
I tried. He won't listen to me.
我试过了  他不听我的
Don't you mean obey?
你是说"服从你"?
He's not your son. He's not your husband.
他不是你儿子  不是你丈夫
He's not your employee.
也不是你的员工
Not everyone has to listen to you.
不是所有人都得听你的
I'll--i'll do this tomorrow.
我明天再弄
Don't go
别走
I got the flowers.
我收到花了
They were from you, right?
-是你送的  对吧
Oh, yeah.
当然
I just have a minute,
我只有一点时间
And I don't want to get into a whole thing with you.
我不想把事情弄大
This won't take long.
不用很久
I don't want to fight anymore. Please, just take the house.
我不希望再起争执了  你就收下房子吧
I don't know how else to say this.
我不知道还能怎么说
What happened yesterday is gonna happen again.
昨天发生的事以后还是会再发生的
It's not gonna be the last time we fight,
那不可能是我们最后一次争吵
'cause that's who we are.
因为我们就是这样的人
Let's not make it worse by living on top of each other.
我们还是别住得太近  让事情更糟吧
Alex...
I'm gonna tell you something I haven't told anybody--
我要告诉你一些我不曾告诉任何人的话...
Not orson, not andrew, just you.
Orson没有  Andrew没有  只有你
I know that I've changed since my business took off,
我知道从事业成功起我有了改变
But I didn't want to admit it.
但我不想承认
I've watched myself become selfish, impatient, rude.
我眼看着自己变得自私  急躁  粗暴
I was never the type to suffer fools gladly,
我从来就不是能和笨蛋友好相处的人
But now I seem to find fools everywhere.
但现在我发现似乎到处都是笨蛋
And I don't want to be that way.
我不想这样的
I need someone who isn't afraid to speak out,
我需要一个不怕对我说真话的人
To call me out when I cross those lines,
当我过分时把我拉回来
And I would love it if you would be that person.
我很乐意你能成为这个人
Did my mother-in-law
我的岳母
Just give me permission to criticize her?
-刚才是不是允许我批评她了?
Yes, I did.
是的
I'm a lucky guy.
我是个幸运的人
Edie.
Edie
Listen, um...
听着...
I'm not happy about you lying to me,
我很不高兴你骗了我
But I think what we have is real, and...
但我想我们所拥有的都是真实的  而且...
I'm not ready to throw it away.
我还没准备好放弃它们
Really?
真的?
And don't tell anyone,
别告诉别人
But I'm at the point in my life
但我现在正处于人生中
Where I could use a happy ending.
想要一个幸福快乐结局的时候
I'll get my stuff.
我去整理东西
Hello?
喂
Jackson, hi. Do you have a sec?
Jackson  你现在方便讲话吗
Sure. Is something wrong?
当然  有什么问题嘛
Uh, no, nothing's wrong. Just...
不  没问题  只是...
We need to talk about this move.
我们得谈谈关于搬家的事
At 5:15 that afternoon,
那天傍晚5:15
Edie williams began calling her friends
Edie Williams开始给朋友们打电话
To inform them that her husband had come home.
告诉他们她的丈夫已经回家了
Sadly, she never got through to any of them.
可惜  她没能联系上任何人
Gabrielle never picked up.
Gabrielle没有接电话
She was too busy watching her children
她忙着看她的孩子们
Being told they had to obey their mother...
被教导必须听从母亲的话...
And trying not to smile.
并努力忍住笑
Lynette wasn't home when edie called.
电话响起时  Lynette不在家
She was with her mother,
她和她母亲在一起
Laughing and sharing stories about the old days...
边笑边回忆过去的故事...
And enjoying every minute of it.
并充分享受这段时光
Bree was outside
Bree在屋外
Showing her future son-in-law color samples
给她的未来半子看她为买给他的房子
For the home she had bought him...
所选的涂料颜色样本...
And smiling politely when they disagreed.
当他们有分歧时  也保持礼貌的微笑
And susan--
而Susan...
Well, she didn't answer
她没接电话
Because she was sitting in her favorite chair
因为她正坐在自己最喜欢的椅子上
With a cup of tea...
喝着一杯茶...
Learning to enjoy, for the first time in her life,
生平第一次  学着去享受
What it was like to be alone.
孤独一个人的滋味